Hit me! Hit me...
打我，打我…
Hit me, hit me again
快点，打我，再打，打我…
C'mon, hit me! As hard as you can
求求你打我，再打
You drink this first
你先喝
No!
不
What're you scared of?
怕什么？
No, I won't drink
不要，我不喝
c'mon, I'll have a sip first, then your turn
我先喝一口，你再喝吧
Let's enjoy ourselves tonight
今天晚上可以有点享受了
I hate you, you're a scoundrel
讨厌，你这个坏人
What's wrong with you?
你怎么搞的！
I didn't mean it
我，我不是有意的
Hit him! Hit him hard
打他，重重的打他
Zhihong
志宏，志宏
It's dirty and smells
又臭又脏，讨厌死了
It's over
好了
-Here you go -Thanks
拿着    谢谢
Get lost, I'm running a business here
走开，走开，别阻我做生意
Beat it
走…
You aren't being paid to read the newspaper
你一天到晚看报纸
Get to work
赶快干活去
Zhihong
志宏
What, you wanna bring the place down?
陈志宏，你想拆房子啊
Are you crazy? Stop breaking my stuff
你神经病，你不要打烂我的东西啊
What's the matter with you?
什么玩儿，他妈的，神经病
Ill wrap this up for you
这个我帮你包起来
Xiujuan, I...
秀…秀娟，我…
Five dollars only, it's cheap
谢谢五块钱，不贵的
Wrap it up
包起来
Please wait
等一等呀
Poor thing, he gets bullied everywhere!
他挺可怜的，到处受人欺负
Have a seat
随便坐
You're hiring a delivery man?
你们请外卖？
The boss is at the back
老板在后面
The boss is right there
老板在那里？
Over there
在那
Boss
老板…
You have to be hardworking
做事要勤快，不能偷懒
And don't wander around on the streets
不能在街上闲荡
10 a.m. to 11p.m.
早上十点到晚上十一点
You'll deliver order by order
有一单就要送一单
Four hundred dollars a month
一个月四百块
You don't eat or sleep here
店里不包吃不包睡
And you'll pay for dishes you break, alright?
打烂碗碟要赔，你干不干？
Yes, I will take the job
干，干
-30,000! -Triple!
三万    碰
Hey, what are you doing here?
喂，你怎么到我这里来呀
It's blood, you poor thing
哎呀，血，好可怜啊
They took your gall bladder
给他们取了蛇胆
And then you got thrown away,
就给扔了
it's so cruel
真是的，他们也太残忍啦
They don't care whether you live or die
不管你的死活，对不对？
Don't be scared
不用怕
I'll take care of your wound
好，我给你包扎一下
Let me get something to stop the bleeding
我拿点东西给你止血
I'll have to attend to the wound...
你给人拿了蛇胆，要不把伤口医好
or else you'll be dead in a week
过不了一个礼拜你就会死了
Don't be scared, there'll be stitches
不要怕呀，我给你缝好
It won't hurt
不要怕疼
Have a good rest, you'll heal in a few days
好好的休息休息，过几天就会好
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
不要紧，我轻轻的缝，不要怕
It's done
接好了
They are too cruel, the gall bladder's use...
他们这些人，为了迷信蛇胆的功用
is exaggerated, they shouldn't have
就把你的胆割了
A snake's life is just as precious as human's
其实蛇的生命跟人一样宝贵
Do you agree?
你说是不是？
You seem to understand me
你好像听懂我的话对不对？
I'm not like them
我告诉你，我跟他们不一样
So stay put and have a good rest
你放心，乖乖地躺下，盖好
Have a good sleep
好好睡觉呀
Xiujuan, I didn't expect to find you here!
秀…秀娟，我…我不知道你会来
Oh, it's you! Look at you
原来是你呀，爬得那么快
Has the wound healed?
伤口好了没有？
Seem to be doing quite well
呃，快好了吗？
Just listen to me
只要你听我的话
You'll recover in a couple of days
再过几天你一定跟以前一样
Look at how you're crawling!
你爬得那么快
Ill name you Xiaobiao, alright?
我叫你小彪，好不好？
Right, Xiaobiao, go to sleep now
好，小彪，乖乖的睡觉吧
Anything you want to tell me?
你还有什么话想告诉我？
I've found another friend
我又找到朋友了
They all got their gall bladders taken out
都是给人拿了胆
Do you want me to help them?
你是不是要我帮他们医好？
No problem, your friends are my friends too
好，你的朋友就是我的朋友
I'll heal them
我一定替他们医好，你放心
You're welcome
不用谢
You're off already? Your job seems to be good
收工了，你这份工作很好
You've worked there for a while now
算是长久的了
I have no qualifications
自己又没本事
All jobs are the same
做什么全是一样的
But I can keep working at this one
不过我总算做得下去
Xiujuan
秀娟
Yes?
什么事
I'd like to take you to a movie
昨天我领了工钱，我想请你看戏
How about the midnight show tonight?
好，午夜场你在翡翠戏院门口等我
See you tonight then
晚上见
Come again
有空，再来坐啊
Hey, your take-away order is here
你们叫的东西来了
Sorry
对不起
Damn, couldn't you be a bit more careful?
死人呀，你什么不长眼睛的！
What are you looking at?
喂，看什么，有什么好看的
Haven't you seen a woman before?
没看过？
Look closer, your mother is similar to me
看清楚点，你妈妈也是这个样子
Have an eyeful! You...
看呀！你…
Damn
他妈的！
I won't charge, look!
看啊！不要钱，赶快看啊
Look!
看啊…！
That's enough, leave him alone
好了，你们不要欺负他了
Get up!
起来
Where did your money go?
钱呢？藏什么去了？
Tell us!
说！
Strip search
把衣服脱了搜
Damn!
他妈的
Go
走
Xiujuan, your father's dying
秀娟，你爸爸病重就快不行啦
You better hurry
你快去呀，不然来不及，快点
Never mind that, c'mon go
这里你不要管，快点去吧
I'll take care of this
这里我帮你收拾
Open up
开门
You're back, think of something
你可回来了，你得赶快想办法
He can't just die here
死在这可不行哪
Father
爸爸
You've to hurry and send him to the hospital
你赶快把他送去医院
Look at him
你看他病成这样子
If he dies here...
要是他死在这儿
I can never rent the room out again
我房子租不出去了
And I'll hold you responsible then
那你可要负责啊！
Be quiet
你静一下好不好！
My father won't die
我爸爸不见得会死吗？
You're quite fierce
哼，你比我还凶呀
Just hurry and get him out of here
你赶紧把他弄出去呀
I don't care even if you leave him on the street
停在街上我可管不着啊
You'll have to think of something, Xiujuan
秀娟，你可要想办法呀
I can't do that
这怎么可以呀
1...Father
我，爸爸
Please call the emergency line...
三姑，你赶快打电话
for the ambulance
叫救护车来呀
The ambulance, alright
救护车呀，我去…
Don't worry, Xiujuan
秀娟，你可放心吧
The hospital will take him
医院会收留你爸爸的
Damn
他妈的…
You're fired, get out of here
妈的，给我滚，明天不要来了
A.
我…
What? You've broken this
我…什么，你看这个打烂了
You're lucky you don't have to pay for it
不叫你赔算好的啦
Boss, I got robbed by some hooligans
老板，我，我被阿飞抢了
I think you're the hooligan, get lost
我看你才是阿飞，滚…
Line up...
排队…
Two tickets
两张
There's only one left
只剩一张啦
I want two tickets
我要两张
-No -Move over
没有      走开…
I want one
一张
Sorry, it's all sold
对不起，客满了
Two tickets...
两张…
I've been telling you to be a call girl...
秀娟，我不早就劝你做舞女
if only you'd listen
你不肯，要是你听了我的话
It'll fetch you money to cure your father
你爸早就好了
And then he won't die, will he?
怎么会死呢？
Hey, you still owe the rent
喂，你欠的房租到底给不给
Hey, I'm talking to you!
喂，我跟你说话呀，你怎么不理
You'll have to pay the rent...
房子是你要租的，我不能让你白住
when will you pay it?
你到底什么时候给呀！
How much does she owe you?
她欠你几个月？
One month's rent
一个月
Forty dollars
四十元，真不要脸
Just because your father's dead
老头死了就想赖租
You still have to pay the rent or...
你再不给
I'll call the police
我就要报警
Fine, here are the forty dollars
好了好了，拿去吧
Xiujuan, you better come with me
秀娟，你还是跟我走吧
I'll take you to my boss, you are pretty
我带你去见大班，凭你这个样
You can start earning money right away
那怕没钱赚
For the time being you can stay with me
你先搬到我那儿去住
You look like a country pumpkin though
看你土里土气也不像样
I'll help you to dress up, you'll be popular
我好好给你打扮，包你会红的
What do you think?
怎么样？
You want to tell me something?
你又要跟我说什么？
Xiaobiao, you're my pal
小彪，你真是我的好朋友
You want to comfort me, right?
你想安慰我是不是
You're so nice, do you know whom I fancy?
你对我真好，你晓得我喜欢的是谁
You wouldn't know
你真的不晓得
Xiujuan, who sells toys over at the street
是对面卖玩具的秀娟
Asked her out for a movie tonight
今天晚上我约她看戏
She didn't show up
她没有来
I trashed her stand in a rage
我一气就把她摊子给打坏
It's my fault, she's very nice to me
是我不好，她这么关心我
I shouldn't have done it
我对不起她
You know exactly what's on my mind
你真懂我的心意
I love being friends with you
我真喜欢跟你做朋友
They all bully me, only you're kind
人家都欺负我，只有你们对我好
This is the best season to savour cobras
现在要吃蛇，最好是吃眼镜蛇
Zhong
阿忠呀
Yes, boss
来了
What can I help you with?
老板叫我什么事？
What's the matter with you?
阿忠，你怎么越来越没出息
Are you stealing my snakes and selling them?
你怎么偷蛇出去卖？
I wouldn't dare do something like that!
老板，我怎么会做这种事情呀
Get to work
赶快去吧
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
The cages look okay, what happened?
笼子也没有坏，蛇怎么会不见？
Are you looking for company?
是不是找小姐？
I want Jin yan
我要金艳
Open up
开门，开门
Have a seat. You've a customer, Jin yan
请坐，阿艳有客人来了
Please. Thanks
请，谢谢
Hurry and take your clothes off
快点，快点脱衣服
What's with you?
怎么啦？
I want another go
我，我还要来
I don't think so
还想玩，那有这么便宜的事
It's your problem, I'll charge you anyway
是你不行，我照收钱
You...
你…
Are you kidding? You've had your fun
笑话，我又不是不给你玩
Pay up now
给钱哪
Have a look at yourself, what a loser!
自己不照照镜子，学人出来玩
Hey the boy might have some money
喂，起来，这小子又有钱
Go...
走…
Search him
搜他的身
Search him, and beat him up
搜他身，还揍他一顿
Damn, you loser
他妈的，没有用的东西
See if you dare to mess with me now
看你敢不敢惹老娘
Oh, it's a snake!
喔，蛇…
Help!
救命
A cobra
眼镜蛇
Calm down
不要动
Bite him
咬啊，咬啊
Bite them all
咬他们…
Damn, it's only a string
他妈的，绳子
Thank you so much
谢谢你
Bite him dead
咬死他…
Bite her
咬她…
Bite her dead
咬死她…
I want more snakes, more...
我要更多的蛇，更多的蛇…
Hurry
快点
What the...!
他妈的
Chen Zhihong
陈志宏
some nerve you've got!
好大的狗胆
How dare you steal from me?
你敢偷老子的蛇，我打死你
Please, Mr. Zhou, the snakes are all here
周老板，蛇全都在这里
Not one less
一条也没有少
I beat you
我打死你
I'll return them all to you, please
我还给你，我求求你
I beg you
我求求你
Please forgive me
周老板，饶我一次
I'll never do it again
我下次不敢
I beg you
周老板，饶了我
Damn
他妈的，还有下次
rll kill you
我不打死你才怪
Damn it
他妈的
The brat is peeping, I'll beat you up
这小鬼，打死你
Help!
救命啊
Where you go?
那里跑
Hold him, the scissors
拿剪刀来把他的剪掉，按住他
Man, wake up
起来
He drinks like you and me
他像我们喝得那么醉
Come on
走吧
Easy
小心
I didn't harm you...
冤有头，债有主，我没有对不起你
Good afternoon
各位观众
This is the News at noon
现在报告中午港闻摘要
Two victims were found dead in a snake shop...
本港昨晚发生一宗离奇恐怖案件
last night. One of them was the shop's owner,
一间蛇铺老板及一名女子
the other was a body of a young woman.
被发现死在蛇店中
According to the police, it's possible that...
据警方透露
the deaths were due to venomous snake bites
两名死者可能被蛇店内之毒蛇咬死
Their bodies were dark purple in color
死者全身呈紫黑色
The male victim is identified as Zhou Fucheng
据查男死者名周福成
Good afternoon, sir
胡先生，你来了
Zhou was the owner of the snake shop
年约四十岁
He was around forty years old
是该蛇店老板
The dead woman is identified as Zhang Jin yan
女死者名张金艳
Twenty two years old
二十二岁
She's a prostitute in the neighbourhood
据闻在附近做舞女为事业
According to the police...
又据警方证实
there are three more bodies...
前在油麻地庙街后巷中
with snake bites found at the alley...
发现之三名男死者
behind Temple Street
亦是被毒蛇咬死
The police warns that a large number...
警方发言人说，命案发生之现场
of poisonous snakes have escaped.
走失大批毒蛇
Citizens are requested to keep a watchful eye
呼吁市民特别注意
And report to the police when they spot...
如发现毒蛇踪迹
the snakes or call the hot line of the...
请立即致电报警
Snakes & Pest Control Unit
或通知农林处防止蛇鼠组
Jeez, you scared the hell out of me!
死鬼，吓死我了
This is the weather report
各位观众现在是潘颖思报告天气
It's a fine day in Hong Kong today
本港天气继续晴朗
with plenty of sunshine
阳光充足
The highest temperature is 25.1 degrees
下午最高气温为摄氏25.1度
And the lowest is 17.9 degrees
昨晚最低为17.9度
The winds will be northerly
今日上午吹北风，空旷地方…
Where's that virgin you promised?
怎么样，你答应我那罐头货呢？
Of course I've got everything prepared
我答应你的事，怎么敢不办呢
Come, I'll show you
来，我带你去看
Fangfang, I can't stand it
芳芳，我实在是受不了啦
Please can I borrow your place now?
你这里现在先借给我用，怎么样？
No
不行
Why not?
为什么不行？
What did you promise me?
你答应我的呢？
You'll have it once the transaction's completed
事成了我一定送给你的
Come on and get dressed
来，你先穿好衣服出去
Half an hour and I'll be set
半个钟头我就搞定了
No, not today
我说，今天不行就不行嘛
Why not? You have my word, I'll reward you
我一定送给你的，为什么不行呢
It's not time yet
时候还没到
See, won't this do?
你看，不行吗？
When the time comes...
你先回去时机成熟
I'll give you a call
我就会打电话告诉你的
Just half an hour... -Now you leave first
半个钟头…    你先走
You must call me, okay
你一定要打电话给我
When did the snakes disappear?
蛇是什么时候跑掉的？
Not sure. We had many customers yesterday
我也不知道，昨天很多人来卖蛇
They were all here
我去抓蛇的时候，它们还在笼里头
But they're all gone this morning
今天早上就不见了
Weren't the cages shut properly?
蛇笼不是关得好好的吗？
But after all they're snakes, it's hard to say
蛇是畜牲，有什么灵性
Old Wu, he lives next door
老吴，这个人住在蛇铺的隔壁
Did you hear any strange noises...
你昨天晚上有没有听到
coming from the shop last night?
蛇铺里有什么特别的声音
No, I was tired and slept the night through
没有，我白天工作很累，睡得很熟
Be careful, there're many escaped snakes
你要小心点，可能逃了不少蛇
Go to a hospital if you get bitten
被蛇咬伤了，要进医院，走吧
Let's go
走吧…
Zhihong, I saw Xiujuan last night
志宏，昨天晚上我看见了秀娟
Xiujuan?
你看到秀娟？
If she wouldn't have called me...
要不是她叫我
I could not have recognized her
我真的不敢看她
She looks really pretty when dressed up
真想不到，秀娟打扮起来那么好看
She's turned into quite a woman; Too bad!
真是黄毛丫头十八变，真可惜呀
Stop it
别说了
Are you alright?
你不舒服呀？
I'm fine
没什么
Forget about it
看开点，有什么办法
Those who have money can dance with her
人家有钱就能搂着秀娟跳舞
They can hold her as close as they want
要搂多紧都行
Sooner or later, she'll become a prostitute
秀娟再干下去，总要陪男人睡觉
If there's a first time, there'll be a second
有第一次，就有第二次，谁有钱
Whoever has money can have a go
谁都能玩她
No
不
Please stop
别这样吧
Why not?
你什么都不答应
You can at least dance with me
跳舞总不能不跟我跳
Mr. Hu, please
胡先生，不要这样嘛
Alright, if you agree to dine out with me...
好了，你答应跟我去消夜
I promise to be a gentleman
我就规规矩矩跳
We can ask Fang to come along
最多叫芳芳一起去
What else are you scared of?
那你还怕什么？
Cheers
干杯
Bottoms up
干，干掉
Another glass, the last one
再来一杯，最后一杯
Had enough!
不要嘛
Don't worry, I'll be here
不要紧嘛，喝晚了我陪你
One last glass
好，最后一杯
Last one
最后一杯
-rll drink with you, cheers -Cheers
我跟你喝，干杯    干杯
I'm just going to the washroom
我去一下洗手间就回来
Fangfang, it's got to be tonight
芳芳，我看秀娟今天晚上一定行了
Can I borrow your place?
借你地方用用怎么样？
No
不行
Alright, go check on her
有办法，你先出去看看她
ain't drunk
我没有醉
Where are you taking her?
喂，你想带她到那儿去？
What a shock!
讨厌
Hey, where's my reward?
我的呢？
Here it is
有
Thanks
谢了
Taxi
的士
Let go of me
放开我，放开我…
Tell me right now
快告诉我
Where did he take Xiujuan to?
那砘锇研憔甏到什么地方去？
Let me go
赶快放开我
Tell me now
你说
Where did he take Xiujuan to?
那砘锇研憔甏到那里去了？
It's none of your business
不关你的事，赶快放开我
Let go or I'll scream
要不我叫了
Where are they?
他们在那里？
Let go of me
放开我，放开我，赶快放开我
Let go
放开我…
Love Motel in Kowloon Tong;
他们在九龙塘爱情别墅
No, no, no
不要，不要…
Hit me! Hit me...
打我…
Please, hit me
求求你，打我…
Forget about it
你心里不舒服，看开点
What can you do?
有什么办法？
You're totally broke
你没钱
Those who have money can dance with her
人家有钱就能搂着秀娟跳舞
They can hold her as close as they want
要搂多紧都行
Sooner or later,
我看秀娟再干下去
she'll become a prostitute
总要陪男人睡觉
If there's a first time, there'll be a second
有第一次，就有第二次
Whoever has money can have a go
谁有钱谁就能玩她
No, No, No
不，不会的…
Xiujuan, whoever has money can touch you
秀娟，谁有钱，谁就能玩弄你
I think you'd be better off dead
我看你还是死了好
Don't worry, it won't hurt a bit
你别怕，死…受不了什么痛苦
It's better than living as a prostitute
谁都可以玩你，那才活不下去呢
Xiujuan, I promise you
秀娟，你放心，谁糟蹋你
I'll take revenge for you
我不会饶过他
Moving away?
搬家？
Xiaobiao, kill for Xiujuan
小彪，小彪，替秀娟报仇
Hu Baochun
胡宝春
You ruined Xiujuan, lucky that I've saved her
你糟蹋了秀娟，要不是我救了她
from her despair
她酒醒后会比蛇咬更痛苦
You're more wicked than venom
你比这些蛇还要毒
I don't think he's in
他好像不在
Look again
再看看
He's not inside
不用找了，他不在里面
He took a lot of stuff with him
昨天他拿了东西走啦
Who are you?
你是干什么的？
I'm the hairdresser next door
我在蛇铺隔壁开理发店
He might have really moved
他可能真的搬走了
Yes, I saw him last night
是啊，昨天晚上我真的
He took a lot of stuff with him
看见他搬了一大堆东西走了
What evidence have you got that he's moved?
有什么证据证明他已经搬走了
Please come with me
你们跟我来吧
-Let's go -OK
走吧      好
Xiaobiao
小彪
Please forgive me, I have no choice
原谅我，我实在不愿意这样做
I just don't want the police to capture you
我只是不愿意警察抓到你们
And they'll torture you
虐待你们
Goodbye, my friends
永别了，我的好朋友
Why've you come back, Xiaobiao?
小彪，你怎么回来了？
Come here
来呀…
You bit me
哎呀，你咬我
Xiaobiao, you bit me
小彪，你咬我，是我
Look at your burn marks
你身上怎么烧成这个样子了
Poor thing, it's my fault...
好可怜呀，小彪，是我不好…
Forgive me then, come on...
原谅我吧，来呀…
Help ! Help!
救命啊，救命啊